

KHURRAM AAMIR

: Profile

Detailed orientated individual experienced in administrative procedures. Oversees day-to-day duties with strong planning and organisation skills to delivers projects in timely manner.

Administrative leader experienced in business operations and team oversight. Seeks opportunities to improve processes, procedures and practices. Excels with minimal supervision and decisively approaches problems.

Employment History

Customer Service Staff at Al Qaza Café November 2023 - Ongoing

HR Manager at Diamond paints, Lahore

August 2022 - October 2023

Director operations at Landlord's {Real Estate, Marketing and Developers), Faisalabad

September 2021- October 2023

Education

Bachelors in business administration with human resource management, University of Agriculture Faisalabad, Pakistan.

October 2018-June 2022

Master in management with project management, BPP University , Manchester

November 2023 - Present

-.. Extra-curricular activities

Coordinator at BMS Society, IBMS, Faisalabad

September 2019 - August 2020

Details

Flat 1, 8 Pine Grove. M14 5QG, Manchester United Kingdom 07831070273

khurramsaikhu897@gmail.com

Date/Place of birth

06/06/2000 Belgium

Nationality

Pakistani

Skills

Facility management

Team leadership

Department management

Contract management

Team player

Client relationships

Languages

English